[rain, wind]
[thunder]
[eerie music]
♪
[shower running]
[panting]
♪
[tense music]
[soft music]
♪
[Sarah]
Ben, come on, not today.
Put that down.
Thanks.
Ben!
Oh, Ben, please don't do that.
What am I gonna do with ya?
[employee]
He's enjoying that.
Doesn't say much, does he?
-Come on, you rascal.
-Oh, here, here, love.
You'll need that
at the checkout.
[register beeping]
[Sarah]
And, er, he, er...
He ate this on the way round.
[cashier]
Couldn't wait, eh, lovie?
-That's eighteen thirteen.
-Mummy!
[Sarah]
Yep, just, um...
I actually think
I'm a bit short.
[cashier]
Oh. Oh, you might have
enough in there, lovie.
[Sarah]
No, erm...
Let's see, let's see.
Actually, could you just
ring these things off?
We've all been there, lovie.
♪
[activist]
Vote for Amy Taylor.
Get your fairness,
equality, and liberty!
♪
Amy Taylor is the future, kids!
Amy Taylor!
-Yeah, thank you.
-She'll stand for everything.
She stands for hope!
Thank you very much.
♪
[Mackers]
Fuck me, diesel-dick.
♪
Good.
No refunds, dickhead.
♪
[Sarah]
Ben, don't play with your food.
♪
Ben.
When the cabin portholes
are dark and green
because of the seas outside,
and the ship goes wop
with a wiggle between
and the steward falls
into the soup tureen
and the trunks
begin to slip and slide
When Nursey lies
on the floor in a...
[Lucy]
Heap!
[Sarah]
And mummy tells you
to let her...
[Lucy]
Sleep!
You aren't waked
or washed or...
-Dressed!
-Well, then you will know
-if you haven't...
-Guessed!
[Sarah]
You're fifty north and forty...
[Lucy]
West!
Yeah!
Do you like that story, Ben?
♪
Alright.
It's time for bed.
-I like the story!
-I know! I like the story too.
Okay, lie down.
Under the covers, yes.
Alright.
♪
I love you.
And I love you.
Sleep.
[TV playing]
[distant car alarm]
Oh, fuck.
Oh, bollocks.
Please, please,
please, please, please.
Thank you, Jesus.
-Hi.
-Name?
[Sarah]
Could I speak to Detective
Baker, or Barnes, please?
They know me, they're looking
after my husband's--
[agent]
I need your name, love.
[Sarah]
No, sorry,
I don't think you understand.
They're looking after
my husband's case.
Stephen Collins.
[agent]
Is this about
a restraining order?
[Sarah]
No.
[agent]
Sarah?
-Yeah.
-Can I call you Sarah?
Yeah.
[agent]
Just let sleeping dogs lie.
[Alice]
He's going to spill that.
[Sarah]
Ben.
Hold your glass properly.
[Alice]
That's a new tablecloth.
He can still hear, can't he?
Yes, he can hear.
[Alice]
I don't understand it,
if he can talk,
why doesn't he just talk?
When's the appointment?
-Thursday.
-I'll go with you.
-There's no need.
-I know you,
you'll just sit there and
let them walk all over you.
If you want to get
anywhere in this life
you have to be
a bit of a bitch.
You'd know, would you, Mam?
[Alice]
Just make sure
you get some answers.
Don't be sitting there
like a pudding.
You're too soft, Sarah.
Always were.
Anything from the police?
No.
[Alice]
That estate.
Nothing good
ever came out of it.
-Stephen came out of it.
-No, he didn't.
He stayed in it
and you joined him.
Well, it's called marriage.
Don't know why you can't
come back here to live.
Do you need money?
No, I'm fine.
-We're fine.
-You don't look fine.
What do you say, princess?
Wouldn't you like
to come live with granny?
[Lucy]
Bitch!
[tense music]
♪
[Sarah]
Ben, do you want
to give these to daddy?
Maybe if you want to say
something to him, you can.
Yeah?
Okay?
♪
That was really good.
[intense music]
♪
[engine turns on]
[laughs]
♪
[revs engine]
[Mackers]
Ah, the fuck?
♪
Hey!
[shouting]
What the fuck!
♪
[Sarah]
Wait! Stop, stop, stop!
-Not a fucking word!
-No, get out! Get out!
Get out! Get out!
[tense music]
[Tito]
Let's go.
Stay!
Don't fucking say a word.
♪
[Mackers]
Fuck!
♪
[Sarah]
No. Stop, stop, stop!
Stop.
[Tito chuckles]
♪
What the fuck
is this? Netflix?
♪
-Stop.
-Who else is here?
-It's just the three of us.
[Tito]
Good.
Can they stop
fucking looking at me?
♪
[Sarah]
Can I put them
in their room, yeah?
♪
It's just here.
[Tito]
Go on.
♪
Sit in here
just one minute, okay?
The man's gonna go.
Just don't open the door.
Promise me, promise me?
[Tito]
You got no fucking towels
in there.
Okay, you don't know me.
[Sarah]
I don't know you.
[Tito]
Even fucking better.
You don't know me.
You seen nothing.
Nothing fucking happened.
-You get me?
-Yeah.
Please go.
[Tito]
"Go?"
Fuck me.
You could be
a wee bit more...fuck.
Hospitality.
Hospitable!
Hospitable.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
♪
[club music]
-Off.
-Hold on.
Hey!
Two wee ones.
[Terry]
Fuck's sake.
♪
[Mackers]
My fucking arm.
♪
Hard day.
[Terry]
Fucking hammerhead, come on.
[Mackers]
Ah.
Will you come on?
Fuck's sake.
[Mackers]
Ah!
♪
Fuck.
[tense music]
♪
No joy.
[Terry]
He's not working
any of our estates.
♪
So what are you doing here?
[Terry]
Everybody's on it.
♪
So what are you doing here?
[Mackers]
We just thought we'd...
♪
-C'mon.
-Fuck off?
♪
[raspy staccato whistles]
[glass shatters]
[man #1 on TV]
Who made the poorest poorer?
Who let youth unemployment
rise higher?
Who made inequality greater?
Not us!
[man #2 on TV]
Don't you dare
lecture us on poverty.
You have failed to help
the poorest people
in our country.
[dialogue continues,
music intensifies]
♪
[knocking on window]
Open the door.
Come on.
Open the fucking door.
Open the door or I'll smash
the fucking glass, let's go!
♪
I'm opening it,
I'm opening it.
♪
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
♪
Every little helps.
I don't want
any part of this.
I don't...I--
[Tito]
What's the panic?
Nobody knows I'm here.
Nobody knows this is here.
It's fucking perfect.
I took ten of these earlier
and sold them.
Twenty quid a pop.
Two hundred quid.
And I have your cut.
Forty percent,
that's for helping me out.
Forty percent there.
No, no, no, no.
I don't want your money.
I don't want this here,
I really just want you to leave.
♪
No. You see,
I got a fucking problem.
I got nowhere to stash this.
I'm living
with two cunts.
You'd need eyes
in your fucking head.
So I was thinking, right,
I keep it here.
Come in and out,
bit at a time.
Nobody knows me.
Nobody fucking sees me.
Nobody would cop on with you
and the two rug rats.
It's perfect.
Five days, right?
I give you a cut.
Everyone's laughing.
It's dope, man,
it's fucking dope.
[Sarah]
Look, I just don't want it.
I just want you to go, yeah?
[stammering]
Stop, stop!
Stop!
♪
[Tito]
That's the way it's gonna be,
alright?
-Mm-hm, mm-hm.
-Or I skin you
and your two
wee fucking pups.
♪
[Sarah]
Ben.
My love, I'm so sorry, okay.
We'll go in a minute,
I promise.
♪
Can you remember,
were you...
♪
Were you standing here
with daddy when...
♪
Did he leave you
in the play-park?
Yeah? Is that what happened?
♪
Do you remember
who daddy was talking to
or if he saw someone?
♪
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'll stop asking.
I'm so sorry.
[knocking]
[banging]
♪
[Tito]
Open the fucking door.
♪
Fucking freezing out there.
You want one?
No.
[can lid snaps]
♪
What about,
what about a beer says you, eh?
[laughs]
♪
Mm.
Business first.
♪
Sold sixteen of these today.
-That's yours, eighty percent.
-Stop it.
-I told you I don't want it.
-Don't start that shit again.
♪
Fuck me.
Look at all these cunts.
Their shiny faces.
Fuck me.
[men on TV continue dialogue]
Your man was right to try
to blow all the fuckers up.
What d'you call him?
That bonfire cunt.
♪
You really like that word.
[Tito]
What?
What is it with you?
You don't like the way I talk,
you don't take a drink.
-Do you smoke?
-No, I don't smoke.
♪
[Tito]
You into God
or some of that shite?
Fucking wee baby Jesus
on the cross.
Telling you if I was there,
it'd have been different.
I'd have pulled my hands out
of those nails
and floated there
in front of all them Romans.
They'd have known
who I was, alright.
♪
[Sarah]
I don't think
that's the point.
[Tito]
What fucking point?
I got these for your rug rats.
-Thought they might still be up.
-Oh, no.
They're asleep. In bed.
[Tito]
Well, give it to them
when they get up.
Or eat them yourself.
You don't do fuck all else.
You must like sweets.
Skinny birds like sweets,
don't they?
Fat girls like cake.
How old are they anyway?
♪
-Six and four.
-Mm.
I like kids.
I'd like to have some.
Have to be
the right woman,
but not some
of these sluts you see.
Fuck. You go into town
at a weekend.
You wouldn't know
what was a prozzie
and what was a good girl.
Your dick'd fall off
with half of them.
So, can I, er...
Can I ask you something?
-Tito.
-Oh, right.
-Uh, Tito, so--
-Tito.
It's not my nickname.
It's my name.
It's different
but I kind of like it.
You know
when you're a kid,
you wanna be the same
as everyone else
but when you get older,
you wanna be different.
What do I call you?
[Sarah]
Sarah.
[Tito]
Oh, good name.
Like an old girl's name.
[Sarah]
Thank you.
Look.
[Tito]
Why is TV always so shit?
All these fucking shows
about eating.
♪
[Sarah]
Have you ever heard of a man
called Stephen Collins?
[Tito]
Is he famous?
[Sarah]
No, he's my....
He was my husband.
[Tito]
He clear off, did he?
[Sarah]
No, he died.
[Tito]
Cancer?
[Sarah]
No, no, it wasn't cancer.
♪
He was murdered.
Stabbed.
Here on the estate.
[Tito]
Jesus.
-Is that him there?
-Yeah, yeah.
[Tito]
Is that you?
[Sarah]
Yeah.
[Tito]
You don't look
nothing like that now, eh!
♪
[Sarah]
Thank you.
[Tito]
You don't, but...
You should tidy yourself up
a wee bit.
Who killed him then?
♪
[Sarah]
I don't know.
♪
Well, nobody saw
what happened or...
At least nobody
came forward.
♪
And they just found Ben.
Crying beside...
Sorry, Ben was with him.
Ben is my son.
♪
I was just wondering
if you knew something.
Anything.
[Tito]
Me? What would I know?
You don't shit
where you live.
♪
Okay, so...
So what happened yesterday?
♪
Was it the police?
[Tito]
Are you stupid or something?
Jesus, no.
Tito, I'm just really,
really confused.
You were running
from someone.
-You were running from?
-Miller's mob.
I stole that bag
off Miller's mob.
Like candy from a fucking shop,
it was.
♪
-Miller's mob?
-Aye, Leo Miller.
He's got the pub in town.
Real fucking animal.
♪
You stole from Leo Miller?
What did I just say?
♪
So, they'll be
looking for you, right?
They'll have put the word out
or they'll have...
[Tito]
Put the word out?
Seriously?
[Tito laughs]
No, I just need a few days
and I'll be set.
If they do
catch up with me,
I've got a few surprises
up my sleeve.
You have to get
out of my house.
You can't come back here.
You really can't.
Oh, don't start
that shit again.
[Sarah]
No.
Tito, please understand,
come on,
I've--I've two little kids,
yeah?
Who just lost their dad.
I just...
I can't have drugs
in the house, I can't.
What'd you call him again?
Stephen.
Aye.
Collins?
-Yeah.
-Aye.
I have heard of him.
He was in the paper.
He was selling.
[Sarah]
Stephen was not selling drugs.
He wasn't dealing drugs.
[Tito]
If it walks like a duck
and talks like a duck,
-it's a fucking duck.
-He had Ben with him, okay,
-that would never have happened.
-Smart.
Using the kid as cover.
So what?
He was a dealer, so what?
[Sarah]
My husband was not
a fucking drug dealer.
[Tito]
A "fucking" drug dealer?
How fucking dare you?
A fucking drug dealer.
[Sarah]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[Tito]
Have a bit
of fucking respect for him.
-Yeah.
-You know,
what we do isn't easy.
What we do is fucking hard,
alright?
♪
Now can I watch this
fucking in peace
without you
in my fucking face?
Fuck.
♪
[soft music]
[Sarah]
Yeah, go on. Pick one.
That one?
Okay!
[employee]
Pay day, love?
Here, how much you
charging anyway?
[Sarah]
What did you just say?
[muttering]
[chuckles]
Mummy's gonna show you
how to eat spaghetti.
Spoon. Fork.
No, Lucy,
not with your fingers!
[laughs]
♪
[distant thumping music]
[grunts]
[vomiting]
[panting]
[soft music]
♪
[Lucy]
Mummy!
♪
[Jimmy]
So I said to myself,
"Who are my two best men?"
Of course, I came up
with the only answer
I could come up with.
Terry. Mackers.
And there they both were,
sitting in the car.
"Am I a fool?," I thought.
Of course I'm not a fool.
I run a big business.
I employ people.
I'm an important man.
I thought,
'course they'll be back.
Two hours tops.
And here we are,
eight o'clock.
My break.
♪
Ben? Ben, don't--
please don't do that, Ben!
Please don't do that.
Okay, come on.
♪
Come on, you okay?
We're just gonna
wash you, okay?
We're just gonna quickly...
Ben, look at me.
Okay,
I'm just gonna wash it off.
No, no, no, stop, stop.
Are you okay?
Ben?
Oh!
It's okay.
Hey, it's okay, it's okay.
♪
Good boy.
It's okay.
♪
Ben, if you feel sick, okay,
you have to tell me.
Yeah?
Please, listen to me.
You have to tell me.
Do you feel okay?
Yeah?
You don't feel sick?
[knocking]
[banging]
-Shh, no, don't move.
-Open the door, Sarah.
-Sarah, open the fucking door.
-Lucy, don't move.
[Tito]
Don't have me
knock the door down.
Open the door.
[glass shattering]
Fuck me.
Now look what
you've made me do.
For fuck's sake.
You stupid fucking wee bitch.
Tito.
What?
What's wrong?
Tito...
Stay here. Stay here.
[Lucy]
Yeah.
[Sarah]
Tito, listen.
No.
Tito.
Tito, it was just a mistake.
He's just a kid, he didn't
know what he was doing.
Look, I'll pay for it.
I'll give you
whatever I have.
It was a mistake.
Yeah? I can fix it.
I'll fix it.
Whatever you want.
Tito, Tito.
Please stop.
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Stop. Get the fuck off me!
[Tito]
Fucking tell me
how much you want me.
[Sarah]
Stop, please.
[Tito]
You want me.
Tell me you want me.
Tell me
you fucking want me
or it's your
fucking little kid.
Your choice.
-I do.
-You want me?
[Sarah]
I do.
-Good girl.
-I do.
I do want you.
I want you.
[Tito]
I always knew you liked me.
Always knew it.
You're so fucking sexy.
[Sarah]
Fuck me.
-You want me to fuck you?
-I do. Please fuck me.
-I don't wanna hurt you.
-I want it to hurt.
I want it to hurt. I do.
[Tito]
I fucking love you.
I love you, Sarah.
Sarah, I fucking want you.
-I want you. I do.
-Sarah, I fucking love you.
You fucking sexy fucking...
Agh!
Fuck!
Jesus! Fuck!
-You fucking little slut!
-Stop! Stop! Stop!
Get off me!
[Tito]
You're the same as all those
other fucking sluts, aren't you?
Aren't you?
You fucking dirty slut!
[raspy breathing]
[grunting]
Fuck.
Oh, god.
[Lucy]
Mummy?
Open the door.
No, don't open the door!
Don't open the door!
-Mummy!
-Don't open the door!
Mummy's coming.
-Fucking hell.
-Oh my god.
-Mummy, mummy, mummy!
Oh my god.
I'm coming!
Mummy!
♪
[Sarah]
It's the man, he...
He just fell down
and hit his head.
He's gonna lie down
for a little bit.
He's just very tired.
Do you wanna go
into the living room
and watch a DVD?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
Ben, will you bring
your sister in?
♪
Close the door.
Tito?
♪
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
♪
[heavy breathing]
-You both okay?
-Yeah.
So, the man's gone.
[Lucy]
Okay.
[Sarah]
The man's gone.
[knocking]
[PC Huxley]
Mrs. Collins?
[knocking]
[Sarah]
Yeah? Yeah, who is it?
[PC Huxley]
Police.
-It's Mrs. Collins, isn't it?
-Yes?
[PC Huxley]
Could you open the door,
Mrs. Collins?
We've had reports
of a disturbance.
[tense music]
♪
Fuck.
[PC Huxley]
As I said, we've had
reports of a disturbance.
[Sarah]
I...
♪
[PC Huxley]
Got yourself a new fella
on the go then, love?
♪
[Sarah]
Sorry..?
Sorry, where are you going?
[PC Huxley]
We've had reports of shouting.
♪
Fight, maybe?
You been drinking?
♪
I'll have to report this.
Anything you want to report?
♪
Well?
Would it matter?
♪
[PC Huxley]
What is it
with women like you?
♪
Excuse me?
[PC Huxley]
You like being
knocked about, huh?
Get out!
Get out of my house!
Get out of my house right now.
[PC Huxley]
We're going.
♪
But don't worry, love
We'll be back.
♪
You better get
your shit together.
For them.
♪
[Sarah]
Lucy, love, mummy's
got some things to do.
-Okay?
-Okay.
♪
Fuck's sake.
[Jimmy]
Tayto?
♪
Tito.
As in General fuckin' Tito.
Yugoslavia, before
all that shit happened.
♪
[Jimmy]
Sometimes you surprise me,
Mackers.
He was in Dunelm yesterday.
Grattan and Forestside today.
♪
-Tito...
-Reilly.
We don't know
where he is yet.
But we'll have that info
by tomorrow.
Tito Reilly.
♪
I'm gonna chop you up
bit by little fucking bit.
[Lucy]
Mummy.
Mummy, mummy.
♪
-It's just for tonight.
-A bar?
[Sarah]
Yeah, it's just a few hours.
I saw a sign in a window.
"Temporary staff."
It's just tonight.
And maybe a night
at the weekend as well.
[Alice]
What bar? I don't know
about you in a bar, Sarah.
[Sarah]
Yeah, well, what you
don't know won't hurt you.
Be good for your gran.
[Lucy]
Bye!
[Sarah]
Bye, love.
Ben, I love you.
[Alice]
When's his appointment?
♪
The hospital?
Oh, it's...
It's tomorrow.
-Had you forgotten?
-No, no, no, it's...
It's, er,
it's just--
I'll be here
first thing, okay?
[Alice]
Maybe you should
forget about
-this thing tonight.
-First thing, okay, Mam?
First thing.
♪
-Sarah?
-What? What? What?
You look wretched.
-Mam, I'm fine.
-No, you're not.
You don't look fine.
I'd say you were
going to meet a man
except you look like
death warmed up.
Mam, I really don't
have time for this.
[Alice]
No time for your health?
-Sarah, you have two children.
-For Christ's sake.
-I'm just saying!
-I know, I know.
That I should
just snap out of it.
-I'm not saying that.
-That's exactly
-what you're saying.
-No!
Mam, I loved Stephen.
-Love...
-Yeah!
Yeah, love.
But that's something
you couldn't understand.
[Alice]
You sound like a bad song.
He was just
the man who came
and took away
your little girl, wasn't he?
[Alice]
Yeah! A little girl
who had her whole future
ahead of her
and now look.
A talented girl!
-He was a drug dealer!
-No.
He was!
-He wasn't!
-He was!
That's what the papers said and
that's what the police think.
Nothing but
a two-bit drug dealer.
Didn't he have a record?
It's--it's not the same thing.
Won't you see sense, Sarah?
I'm sorry,
but it has to be said.
Okay, great,
and now that you've said it,
you can go fuck off.
♪
[Jimmy]
Tito Reilly.
[interrogatee #1]
We don't know
where the fuck he is.
I swear.
Honest.
He never came back
last night.
[interrogatee #2]
Look, we don't really
know him anyway, man.
Don't call me "man."
Find some other noun.
[interrogatee #2]
But we don't.
He just comes and goes.
[Jimmy]
Give me that again,
with the noun.
[interrogatee #2]
He just comes and goes...
♪
Sir?
[Jimmy]
Better.
♪
Tito.
Only Tito I ever heard of
was General Tito.
Presidente of Yugoslavia.
Then he died.
And the place went to shit.
♪
Same happened in Iraq.
Old Saddam
might have been a cunt,
but the country functioned
with those
cast-iron balls of his.
People just went about
their normal, everyday business.
♪
Take Syria at the minute.
Why are the Russians
propping up the regime?
Putin and Assad.
[pops lips twice]
Two more cunts.
♪
But they know
about leadership.
And fear.
Real-politik,
they call it.
♪
You interested
in real-politik?
♪
When the status-quo
is threatened,
the ends justify the means.
Thank you, Terry.
[gleeful exclamation]
♪
In other words,
we must think
of the greater good,
gentlemen.
You do recognize the metaphor
in this situation, huh?
Metaphor.
Gimme a metaphor.
♪
[interrogatee #2]
Black, black as coal.
No, no, no.
That's a simile.
Black as coal.
[interrogatee #1]
Fuck me!
Don't, please don't. Please!
Fuck, please, please!
Jesus Christ.
On me fucking shoe, you twat!
Listen to me,
listen to me.
[rhythmic mouth sounds]
-Please, please.
-Oh, don't.
Oh, wipe your face.
-Please, please.
-Wipe your face.
[interrogatee #2 groaning]
-Please.
-Er, not please, please, please.
-That's not a metaphor.
-Uh--
[Jimmy]
Let me give you one.
-In deep shit.
-No, no, please!
[Jimmy]
Yeah, yeah. In deep shit.
♪
You don't mind if I get rid
of some change, do you?
[cashier]
Can always use the change, love.
♪
There's bound
to be easier ways, love.
♪
Just throw him out.
It's better than all this.
[laughs]
♪
[panting]
I'm just gonna do it.
[labored breathing]
[rapid breathing]
[saw grinding]
[vomiting]
[gasping]
God.
[hyperventilating]
[axe thudding]
[screams]
[gasping, panting]
♪
[panting]
[crying]
♪
[panting]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder intensifies]
[shower running]
[panting]
Hi, Mam.
Hi!
-Hi.
-Mummy.
[smooching]
[Sarah]
Hi, love!
Are you both ready, yeah?
I just have to talk
to your gran.
[Lucy]
Okay.
[Sarah]
Mam.
Look, about yesterday, I just...
[Alice]
What use are apologies?
I never thought I would see
the day when my daughter--
[door slams]
This looks quite nasty.
[Jimmy]
You don't say.
[doctor]
How did you do it, sir?
Wanking.
[muffled speaking]
[therapist]
Do you like playing
with your sister?
Tito.
[soft music]
♪
[Sarah]
Love...
That man won't
bother us anymore.
Please stop saying his name.
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
♪
[therapist]
Bottom line, Mrs. Collins,
Ben will talk again.
♪
Put simply, Ben doesn't want
to talk about what happened.
Or even more simply,
he hasn't a clue
how to talk about it.
He can't rationalize it.
Make sense of it.
So his brain
has locked it down.
Shunted it off into
a dusty corner somewhere.
And with it, his speech,
because his brain knows
that once he talks,
he'll go searching
in that dusty corner.
And that's something
his brain, for the moment,
doesn't think
he'll be able to deal with.
♪
I'm sorry.
I know it's one thing
giving an explanation.
It's another
giving a solution,
but this isn't
an exact science.
[phone ringing]
♪
Now.
[Sarah]
A dusty corner of his brain?
[therapist]
It's a metaphor, Sarah.
It's, you know,
if you want--
[Sarah]
Don't tell me
what a metaphor is.
I know what a metaphor is.
Just like I know
what rationalize means.
[awkward laugh]
♪
[Lucy]
Tito!
Lucy, please, please stop.
[Lucy]
Tito.
[Sarah]
Love, please stop. Come on.
Going home.
♪
[Lucy]
Not Tito.
♪
Where were you rammed?
I know it was on the estate.
I mean where
exactly were you rammed?
♪
[knocking]
[Emily]
Mrs. Collins?
My name is Emily Scott.
I'm with Social Services.
♪
You will need to get that
properly fixed, Mrs. Collins.
[Sarah]
Yeah, I'm getting it fixed.
[Emily]
Now, you understand
that Social Services
need to follow up
on such reports.
But this is just a chat,
nothing formal.
Now, according
to the police report,
there was a disturbance?
The house was unkempt?
♪
-Unkempt?
-Untidy.
♪
I had just made dinner
and I didn't have time
to wash the dishes.
[Emily]
Believe me,
I'm a mother too.
After dinner
at our house,
you'd think a bomb
had gone off in the kitchen.
♪
There was evidence
of alcohol
having been consumed.
I had wine with dinner.
[Emily]
How much, would you say?
I know these questions may
seem intrusive, Mrs. Collins,
but believe me, I am here
in a supportive capacity.
♪
I am aware
that your husband died.
♪
He was murdered.
[Emily]
I'm very sorry.
♪
It must be difficult for you.
My husband being murdered?
Yes, quite difficult.
[Emily]
I mean coping.
[Sarah]
What, with the fact
that the police
have done nothing
to find his killer?
-I mean with the children.
-No.
♪
They're my children.
I'm their mother
and I love them.
[Emily]
I'm sure you do.
♪
Yes, I do.
[Emily]
And I'm sure
we're all agreed
that they are
what is most important
in all of this, Sarah.
♪
Tell me what happened
the other night, Sarah.
♪
Okay, look, I...
[Emily]
Yes?
♪
Do you use a vibrator?
[Emily]
Do I what?
The man who was here.
The disturbance.
I stabbed him in the eye
with my vibrator.
[Emily]
I don't understand.
[Sarah]
Well, he wanted to fuck me
and I didn't want to.
So I had to stab him in the eye
with my vibrator.
That's what happened
the other night.
♪
[Emily]
You want me to write that
in my report?
It's what happened
the other night.
♪
[kisses]
Goodnight.
Goodnight, love.
-Story!
-No, your mam's too tired.
[Lucy]
Whale, whale!
[Sarah]
Do you wanna?
Is that okay with you, Ben?
Okay.
But a quick one, okay?
[Lucy]
Okay.
Do you know your gran
used to read this book to me?
[Lucy]
No, I didn't know that.
[Sarah]
She did.
"In the sea
once upon a time,
o my best beloved,
there was a whale
and he ate fishes.
He ate the starfish
and the garfish.
The crab
and the dab.
And the plaice
and the dace.
And the skate
and his mate.
And the mackerel
and the pickereel.
And the really, truly,
twirly-whirly eel.
All the fishes
he could find in the sea
he ate with his mouth.
Till at last there was
only one small fish
left in all the sea.
And he was a small stute fish.
And he swam a little
behind the whale's right ear
so as to be out of harm's way.
And the whale stood up
on his tail and said
'I'm hungry.'"
♪
"And the small stute fish said,
in a small stute voice,
'Noble and generous whale,
have you ever tasted man?'
'No,' the whale said.
'What is it like?'
'Nice,'
said the small stute fish.
'Nice, but nubbly.'"
♪
[Mackers]
I said to this wee bird
the other night.
-Right.
-"Fancy a fuck and a pizza?"
She says, "What?"
Here's me,
"Do you not like pizza?"
[Terry]
You're a dirty dog, Mackers.
♪
[garbage truck approaching]
[garbage rattling]
♪
[chuckling]
[Terry]
Busted.
-Where?
-Corner.
♪
[Mackers]
Bingo.
Make the call.
♪
[Sarah]
We're just gonna go out
for a second.
Okay.
Yeah, nice and warm.
[banging]
♪
We're just gonna
go out this way.
Shh, shh, we're just
gonna go this way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here we go, here we go.
♪
Cold?
No, we're gonna go this way--
♪
Where's your boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
[Mackers]
Tito.
Is he in there?
[Sarah]
I don't know who that is.
♪
Wait, Ben, Ben, Ben!
Ben!
Ben, stop!
[tires screech]
♪
[Jimmy]
It's alright, lads.
[sanitation worker]
What's going on here?
♪
[Jimmy]
What's going on here
is none of your business.
If you were wise men,
you'd get back
in your lorry
and fuck the fuck off.
[sanitation worker]
But we're not wise men.
We're bin men.
[Jimmy]
A bin man.
And a fucking cunt.
[Sarah]
Ben, are you okay?
[Jimmy]
How low can you go?
[Sarah]
Ben, is that him?
Is that the man?
[grunting]
Yeah?
♪
We're gonna run.
[thuds]
♪
[laughter]
[Alice]
What are you doing here
in the dark?
No, leave it off.
Sorry, please.
[Alice]
Do you want
to eat something?
No.
[Alice]
You should eat.
There isn't a pick on you.
You look like what's-her-name
out of Popeye.
Olive Oyl.
You look like Olive Oyl.
[Sarah]
You always had a way
of putting things.
Always knew
how to make me feel great.
Just saying.
You were such a good mam.
-Now you're scaring me.
-No, it's true.
You were.
You were steadfast.
That's the word.
You weren't much
for hugs and kisses.
But you were always there.
[Alice]
I feel my age.
First time I've really begun
to feel it.
Makes you...
♪
What you're going through,
I know very little about it.
Maybe nothing.
♪
When your father died...
What did I feel?
♪
When we married...
...we were each other's
last chance.
♪
I wanted a baby
and, I don't know,
I suppose he wanted sex.
[Sarah]
Jesus, Mam.
[giggling]
♪
[Alice]
But I don't think
I ever loved him.
♪
I was fond of him
maybe at one time, but love?
♪
Certainly nothing
like you and Stephen.
♪
I'm sorry.
You're the only person
I've ever really loved.
♪
And it breaks
my crooked old heart.
♪
[Sarah]
I know, Mam.
♪
I know that, Mam.
Don't think I don't know.
♪
When the cabin portholes
are dark and green
because of the seas outside.
And the ship goes wop
with a wiggle between.
And the steward falls
into the soup tureen.
And the trunks begin
to slip and slide.
When Nursey falls
on to the floor in a...
[Lucy]
Heap.
[Sarah]
And mummy tells
you to let her...
[Lucy]
Sleep!
♪
[Sarah]
You aren't waked
or washed or...
[Lucy]
Dressed!
♪
Well, then you will know
if you haven't...
[Lucy]
Guessed!
♪
Ben, that man...
He is never going
to hurt us again.
Do you hear me?
Ben, please look at me.
Please.
♪
Never.
When you are waked
or washed or dressed,
well, then, you will know
if you haven't guessed.
You're fifty north
and forty...
[Ben]
West.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
♪
What the fuck?
Door was open.
-How did you--
-The door...was open.
♪
Nice photos.
You want Tito?
Fine, I'll give you Tito.
But this is going to end.
You have to stay away
from me and my children.
♪
My children and I.
Just tell me where he is!
All this dragging of feet
is so unnecessary.
I will bring him.
♪
I will bring him
to your place in one hour.
Is that so?
Now, get the hell
out of my house.
♪
I'll be waiting.
Mam?
Mam!
♪
[Alice]
What's wrong?
Were you talking to someone?
[Alice]
No, no, I was just
talking to myself.
Myself.
♪
[heavy metal music]
[Ray]
Do you come here often, love?
♪
[throat singing]
Love?
[Mackers]
Fuck off.
After you.
♪
[throat singing]
Fuck off, Ray.
♪
[music becomes muffled]
[tense music]
♪
Get in!
Where's Reilly?
[Sarah panting]
♪
[stammers]
I said!
♪
Open...
Just open the bag.
♪
Yeah?
Open the bag.
[dark music]
♪
What the fuck?
[Sarah panting]
[Sarah]
You wanted Tito?
Yeah?
♪
Here he is!
[Terry]
She's a fucking psycho.
♪
Look at him!
What?
Fucking look at him!
[giddy laughter]
♪
[Jimmy]
Jesus!
[laughs]
Woman!
You got some balls, woman!
But what?
What do you expect?
What do you want?
♪
[Jimmy laughs]
Do you even remember
my husband's name?
♪
[Jimmy]
What?
[laughs]
Do you remember
my husband's name?
♪
Wha--
[Terry]
Who's your husband?
Stephen Collins.
♪
[Jimmy]
Say that again.
♪
My husband
was Stephen Collins.
♪
[panting]
I cut him up!
Don't think
I won't shoot you.
Wait, stop!
[gunshot]
♪
[Terry]
Get back!
[gunshot]
[grunts]
♪
[gunshot]
[panting]
♪
Fucking shot me, you bitch!
Why did you do it?
[Jimmy]
Fuck you, cunt.
[Sarah]
Why did you kill my husband?
[Jimmy grunting]
♪
Stuck his nose where
it didn't belong, didn't he?
♪
I was looking for a guy
who owed me money.
♪
I found him.
[panting]
Your fella saw us.
Tried to play good Samaritan,
didn't he?
♪
Not my favorite
Bible story.
Stupid fucking story,
if you ask me.
♪
After I put the word about.
[wry laugh]
The police are like
anybody else.
Believe what
they want to bel--
[gunshots]
Fuck you, cunt.
[panting]
[Mackers]
Fucking bitch.
[groans]
Ah, fuck.
[Mackers panting]
♪
[groaning]
Ah, fuck!
[music intensifies]
♪
[panting]
[reporter]
...which, according
to police sources,
bears all the hallmarks
of a gangland killing.
The triple murder
is being linked
to the discovery
of body parts
in a nearby
waste recycling center.
This, too, would suggest
a feud between rival drug-lords
and might also suggest
paramilitary influence.
[Sarah]
Ben?
Lucy?
Lucy.
What have I told you two?
Huh?
[employee]
They'll never listen.
[Sarah]
Come on.
[employee]
Here, must be paying well.
Might even be tempted myself.
[Sarah]
Do you want to pick
your favorite chocolate?
And one for Lucy too.
Now, say "thank you"
to the nice man.
-Thank you!
-What?
[Lucy]
Thank you!
[Sarah]
Probably gonna need this
at the till.
[employee]
What's your game?
[Sarah]
You're gonna pay for this.
Otherwise I'm gonna walk
right over to the office
and talk to your Floor Manager
and tell him that you flashed
your cock at my children.
[employee]
What?
[stammers]
What kind of a thing
is that to say?
[Sarah]
Exactly.
[employee]
But he'd never believe you.
[Sarah]
But would it matter?
[bright music]
♪
Come on.
This way.
♪
[Lucy]
Cock!
♪
[music darkens]